She fought for her country's freedom at the cost of her own.
Milada is a drama, history film directed by David Mrnka.
Pre-WWII Czech democratic politician Milada Horáková was one of the
first victims of the communist regime in Czechoslovakia.
Opposing the 1948 coup but not leaving the country, she was arrested and tried for
treason on fabricated charges in a show trial broadcast on the radio.
Milada Horáková, played by Ayelet Zurer.
Bohuslav Horák, played by Robert Gant.
Jana Horáková Age 6, played by Daniel Rchichev.
Jana Horáková Age 13, played by Karina Rchichev.
Jana Horáková Age 57, played by Taťjana Medvecká.
Milada's Sister, played by Vica Kerekes.
Milada is a 2017 Czech biographical film written,
produced and directed by David Mrnka.
Produced in the English language, it stars Israeli
actress Ayelet Zurer as Milada Horáková.
The film was a Czech-American co-production by Loaded Vision Entertainment.
The movie follows the life of Milada Horáková (1901–1950), a politician who was hanged by the
Communist Party of Czechoslovakia on fabricated charges of conspiracy and treason.
The film won two Czech Lions (costume design; makeup and hairstyling).
The film explores themes of death sentence, czechoslovakia,
based on true story, communism, historical drama.
The tone is emotional.